softlate.com 2013-12-25

# Softlate

### Privacy Policy

www.softlate.com protects and guarantees security in the collection and processing of the data that is affected through this site as well as the strict compliance with the current policy with regards to data protection. The following paragraphs inform about our procedures of data collection and processing.

Through this website personal data will be collected with the purposes of managing and providing our services, sending internal commercial promotions and providing information of interest for users, related the services of the site.

These data are stored in a archive of personal data whose www.softlate.com is holder, properly registered at the Agency of Data Protection. Nevertheless, the data holder may communicate his/her intention not to be sent any more information at any moment, by sending an email to [contact@softlate.com](mailto:%20contact@softlate.com)

**Identification and contact data of the Company.**

www.softlate.com is a product of Tuguu SL ([http://www.tuguu.com](http://www.tuguu.com/)) is a Spanish company based in Santa Cruz de Tenerife (Islas Canarias) Av. Barranco de las Torres Nº 10 of 4A. Terms of use and Privacy Policy - Should users wish to file any complaints, they can contact the company through the support form available in the site or sending a message to the email address [contact@softlate.com](mailto:%20contact@softlate.com)

**Additional Information We Collect.**

When you use our Services, we collect tracking information like IP address, browser and operative system you are using, details about your computer hardware, the applications you have installed on your PC, and pages you visited on our Sites. None of this information is to identify you personally. 

**Cookies.**

You can choose if you want to accept or reject all the cookies by modifying your browser preferences. But it is possible that by rejecting all cookies you may be unable to use our Services.

**Security.**

We try not to collect information about children under the age of 13, but sometimes it's very difficult to make sure that the person who is providing the information is above 13, that's why we encourage parents and guardians to visit the websites that their children visit. The means with which website operators collect and use the personal information of children under 13 is regulated by The Federal Trade Commission (“FTC”) and it's followed by the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (the “Act”). For more information about the Act and children's on-line privacy in general you can visit the FTC's web site at [www.ftc.gov/privacy](http://www.ftc.gov/privacy) and for safety tips on privacy visit [www.OnGuardOnline.gov](http://www.onguardonline.gov/).

**International Policy.**

Our Services are hosted by servers in United States & France. When you submit your personal information you should be aware that you understand and consent, to its transfer, storage and processing in United States & France. Alternatively, if you would like, contact us via e-mail at [contact@softlate.com](mailto:%20contact@softlate.com)
